Guide to the Rice University Association of Rice Alumni records, 1922-2019 UA 003
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series IV. Events and Programs
  - Alumni Groups Papers, 1997-2000 (2/2) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Rice Alumni Institute, 1975-1989 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Beer Bike Race
    - Beer Bike Race Papers, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Beer Bike Race Papers, 1984-1986 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Blood Drive, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Majors Day, 1983-1986 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - New Activities, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Rice Business Network, 1995-1999 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Rice Today Programs, 1962-1965 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Rice Rings, 1967-1971 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Rice University Review, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Rice Woman's Club
    - Rice Women's Club (1/2) (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Rice Women'S Club (2/2) (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Senior Picnic, 1980-1986 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Workshops, Seminars, Lectures
    - Distinguished Scholar Lectures, 1962-1967 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Getting a Job Workshop, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Survival Seminar, 1978-1980 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Mr. Bray's Talk, January 13, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Other Workshops, Seminars, and Lectures (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Series V. Rice-Related Correspondence
  - Correspondence (Alphabetical by Topic)
    - Correspondence--Alumni (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence--Class Agents Frontier, 1916 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence--Discontinuance of Prayer (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence--Entrance Requirements (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence--Football Film (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence--Lost Alumni, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence--Medallions (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence--Meeting Notices (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence--Memorials (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence--Mergers (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence--Name Change (Institute to University) (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence--Owl Club (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence--Playing Cards (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence-- R Association (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence--Tours (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence--Tuition (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence 1968-69, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence--Miscellaneous (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Class Letters
    - Class Letters, 1916-1917 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Class Letters, 1918-1919 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Class Letters, 1920-1921 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Class Letters, 1922-1923 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Class Letters, 1924-1926 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Class Letters, 1927-1928 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Class Letters, 1929-1930 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Class Letters, 1931-1932 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Class Letters, 1933-1936 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Class Letters, 1937-1939 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Class Letters, 1940-1941 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Class Letters, 1942-1976 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Letters Addressed to Specific Groups
    - Letters from Association of Rice Alumni President to Freshmen and Seniors (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Letters to Degree Candidates, 1955-1969 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Letters from Dr. Gillis, 1994-2000 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Letters to Outstanding Students, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Letters to President's Honor Roll Students (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - [Letters in this folder have been removed to Early Rice Institute records, call # UA 101, Series VI, as correspondence between W. M. Rice, A. B. Cohn, and business partners, 1900] (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Series VI. Related Papers and Materials
  - Annual Report, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Brochures, Announcements (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Brochures, Flyers (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Calendars, 1995-2000 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Class Reports (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Estate Planning, 1965, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Film (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Film--A History of Rice (68), 1988 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Invitations, 1961-1963, 1995-2000 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Newsclippings and Press Releases (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Newsletters, 1920, 1922-24, 1929, 1931, 1955, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Rice Memorial Center, 1955, 1957, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Rice Memorial Center Fundraising and Gift-giving, 1938-1978 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Travel, 1973, 1987-1988, 1992, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Presidential Search (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - George Erik Rupp's Inauguration, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Sallyport (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Photographs of Alumni (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Photos of ARA Presidents (Box 15)
  - Raw footage of Malcolm Lovett audio on Channel 1 (5 copies) (Box 16)
  - ARA002 Association of Rice Alumni Film Reel (Box 16)
- Series VII. Surveys
  - Questionnaire Papers, 1948-1964 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Complete Set of Data from Alumni Survey, 1979 (1/3) (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Complete Set of Data from Alumni Survey, 1979 (2/3) (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Complete Set of Data from Alumni Survey, 1979 (3/3) (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Survey of Alumni as a part of an Evaluation of the Undergraduate Experience at Rice University (1/4) (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Survey of Alumni as a part of an Evaluation of the Undergraduate Experience at Rice University (2/4) (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Survey of Alumni as a part of an Evaluation of the Undergraduate Experience at Rice University (3/4) (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Survey of Alumni as a part of an Evaluation of the Undergraduate Experience at Rice University (4/4) (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Survey Responses, 1979 (1/2) (Box 18)
  - Alumni Survey Responses, 1979 (2/2) (Box 19)
- Series VIII. Awards
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted items in this series are marked in the inventory. Please contact the Association of Rice Alumni regarding access.
  - Awards Subcommittee Papers, 1937-1947 (1/2) (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Awards Subcommittee Papers, 1937-1947 (2/2) (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Awards Subcommittee Papers, 1984-1987 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Awards--Invitations & Programs, 1980-2001 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Lists of Alumni Award Recipients and Nomination Form (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Laureates (Honors) Dinner
    - Laureates Dinner, 1992-1999 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Laureates Dinner, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Laureates Dinner, 1997-1999 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Laureates Dinner, 2000-2005 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Laureates Dinner, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Laureates Dinner, 2007 (1/2) (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Laureates Dinner, 2007 (2/2) (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Laureates Dinner, 2008 (1/2) (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Laureates Dinner, 2008 (2/2) (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Laureates Dinner, 2009 (1/2) (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Laureates Dinner, 2009 (2/2) (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Laureates Dinner, 2010 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Laureates Dinner, 2011 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Laureates Dinner, 2012 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Laureates Dinner, 2013 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Laureates Dinner, 2014 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Laureates Dinner, 2015 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Laureates Dinner, 2016 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Laureates Dinner, 2017 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Laureates Dinner, 2018 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Laureates Dinner, 2019-2021 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Other Awards
    - Honorary Alumnus Award (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Awards--Special (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Awards--Teaching (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Certificate of Merit & Medal of Honor (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Medal for Distinguished Service (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Young Alumni Achievement Award, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Distinguished Alumni Award
    - Distinguished Alumni Award Papers, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Distinguished Alumni Award Papers, 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Distinguished Alumni Award Papers, 1983-1989 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Distinguished Alumni Award Papers, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Distinguished Alumni Award Recipients, 1976-2016; 163781
      - Tracey Yerkes Thomas '21, 1976; 164073 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Charles William Goyen '37, 1977; 164074 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Norman Hurd Richer '16, 1978; 164075 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Herbert Allen '29, 1978; 164076 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - Robert Woodrow Wilson '57, 1979; 164077 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - George R. Brown '20, 1980; 164078 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - George H. Richter '26, 1980; 164079 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - William F. Kieschinck '47, 1981; 164080 (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - S.I. Morris '35, 1981; 164081 (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - Frank J. Low '57, 1982; 164082 (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - George W. Mackey '38, 1982; 164083 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Charles J. Meyers '45, 1982; 164084 (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Teresa J. Vietta '49, 1982; 164085 (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - William McVey '27, 1983; 164086 (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Walter P. Moore '27, 1983; 164087 (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Sam P. Worden '35, 1983; 164088 (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Harry J. Chavanne '33, 1984; 164089 (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - John A. Graves III '42, 1984; 164090 (Box 21, Folder 22)
      - M. Kenneth Oshman '62, 1984; 164091 (Box 21, Folder 23)
      - David Rooke '43, 1984; 164092 (Box 21, Folder 24)
      - Louis J. Girard '41, 1985 (1/2); 164093 (Box 21, Folder 25)
      - Louis J. Girard '41, 1985 (2/2) (Box 21, Folder 26)
      - William P. Hobby, Jr. '53, 1985; 164094 (Box 21, Folder 27)
      - Roland W. Schmitt '51, 1985; 164095 (Box 21, Folder 28)
      - Elwyn L. Simons '53, 1985; 164096 (Box 21, Folder 29)
      - Marshall D. Gates, Jr. 36, 1986; 164097 (Box 21, Folder 30)
      - Jack M. McGinty '57, 1986; 164098 (Box 21, Folder 31)
      - Larry J. McMurtry '60, 1986; 164099 (Box 21, Folder 32)
      - Carl R. Woodring '40, 1986; 164100 (Box 21, Folder 33)
      - James E. Gunn '61, 1987; 164101 (Box 21, Folder 34)
      - Frank B. Ryan ''58, '62, '65, 1987; 164102 (Box 21, Folder 35)
      - Gloria McDermith Shatto '54, 1987; 164103 (Box 21, Folder 36)
      - Mary Elizabeth Johnston '41, 1988; 164104 (Box 21, Folder 37)
      - Burton J. McMurtry '56, '57, 1988; 164105 (Box 21, Folder 38)
      - Dennis P. Sullivan '63, 1988; 164106 (Box 21, Folder 39)
      - Charles Daeschner '42, 1989; 164107 (Box 21, Folder 40)
      - E. Fay Jones '51, 1989; 164108 (Box 21, Folder 41)
      - James G. Treybig '63, 1989; 164109 (Box 21, Folder 42)
      - Gilbert R. Whitaker, 1989; 164110 (Box 21, Folder 43)
      - J. Howard Creekmore '26, 1990; 164111 (Box 21, Folder 44)
      - Donna Paul Martin '57, 1990; 164112 (Box 21, Folder 45)
      - A. Frank Smith Jr. '37, 1990; 164113 (Box 21, Folder 46)
      - G. King Walters '53, 1990; 164114 (Box 21, Folder 47)
      - James E. Bailey '66, '69, 1991; 164115 (Box 21, Folder 48)
      - Thomas H. Cruikshank '52, 1991; 164116 (Box 21, Folder 49)
      - Peter Masterson '57, 1991; 164117 (Box 21, Folder 50)
      - Karen Padgett Davis '65, '69, 1991; 164118 (Box 21, Folder 51)
      - Charles M. Blair '31, 1992; 164119 (Box 21, Folder 52)
      - Robert L. Clark '63, 1992; 164120 (Box 21, Folder 53)
      - Walter G. Hall '28, 1992; 164121 (Box 21, Folder 54)
      - Robert B. Morin '59, 1992; 164122 (Box 21, Folder 55)
      - William D. Broyles Jr. '66, 1993; 164123 (Box 21, Folder 56)
      - Alan J. Chapman, '45, 1993; 164124 (Box 21, Folder 57)
      - Robert J. Cruikshank '51, 1993; 164125 (Box 21, Folder 58)
      - Melvin Perelman '52, 1993; 164126 (Box 21, Folder 59)
      - C. Wayne Bardin '57, 1994; 164127 (Box 21, Folder 60)
      - Jess B. Bessinger '43, 1994; 164128 (Box 21, Folder 61)
      - Charles S. Matthews '41, '43, '44, 1994; 164129 (Box 21, Folder 62)
      - Hershel M. Rich '45, '47, 1994; 164130 (Box 21, Folder 63)
      - Clay M. Armstrong '56, 1995; 164131 (Box 21, Folder 64)
      - Anita Katherine Jones '64, 1995; 164132 (Box 21, Folder 65)
      - Edward W. Kelley, Jr. '54, 1995; 164133 (Box 21, Folder 66)
      - Walter P. Moore, Jr. '59, '60, 1995; 164134 (Box 21, Folder 67)
      - Fance Franck '48, 1996; 164145 (Box 21, Folder 68)
      - Claude Payne '54, 1996; 164146 (Box 21, Folder 69)
      - C.J. Peters '62, 1996; 164147 (Box 21, Folder 70)
      - George Williams '23, 1996; 164148 (Box 21, Folder 71)
      - Nancy Stooksbury Cole '64, 1997; 164149 (Box 21, Folder 72)
      - Robert F. Curl '54, 1997; 164150 (Box 21, Folder 73)
      - John Doerr '73, 1997; 164151 (Box 21, Folder 74)
      - William S. Mackey, Jr. '43, 1997; 164152 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - James L. Kinsey '56, '59, 1998; 164153 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Elizabeth Vickrey Lodal '66, 1998; 164154 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Jan M. Lodal '64, 1998; 164155 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - W. Bernard Pieper '53, '54, 1998; 164156 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Thomas A. Tombrello '58, '60, '61, 1998; 164157 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Gertrude Barnstone '45, 1999; 164158 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - L. Henry Gissel '58, 1999; 164159 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Laza J. Greenfield '55, 1999; 164160 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Nils Muench '49, '50, '55, 1999; 164161 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Griffini Smith Jr. '63, 1999; 164162 (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - H. Randolph Bailey '64, 2000; 164163 (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - Catharine Savage Brosman '55, '57, '60, 2000; 164164 (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - Kathleen A. Desilva '77, 2000; 164165 (Box 22, Folder 14)
      - Wylie Walker Vale, Jr. '64, 2000; 164166 (Box 22, Folder 15)
      - Mary Fanett Wheeler '71, 2000; 164167 (Box 22, Folder 16)
      - Teveia Rose Barnes '75, 2001; 164168 (Box 22, Folder 17)
      - Bruce Wall Dunlevie '79, 2001; 164169 (Box 22, Folder 18)
      - Cynthia Jane Miller '65, 2001; 164170 (Box 22, Folder 19)
      - Vladimir Rokhlin '83, 2001; 164171 (Box 22, Folder 20)
      - E. Brad Thompson '55, 2001; 164172 (Box 22, Folder 21)
      - Alberto R. Gonzales '79, 2002; 164173 (Box 22, Folder 22)
      - Ken Kennedy '67, 2002; 164174 (Box 22, Folder 23)
      - Nancy B. Rapaport '82, 2002; 164175 (Box 22, Folder 24)
      - Hector Ruiz '73, 2002; 164176 (Box 22, Folder 25)
      - John Urquhart '55, 2002; 164177 (Box 22, Folder 26)
      - Jane G. Evans '46, 2003; 164178 (Box 22, Folder 27)
      - J. Michael Fitzpatrick '74, 2003; 164179 (Box 22, Folder 28)
      - Arun Netravali '69, '71, 2003; 164180 (Box 22, Folder 29)
      - Harry M. Reasoner '60, 2003; 164181 (Box 22, Folder 30)
      - John E. Wolf, Jr. '61, 2003; 164182 (Box 22, Folder 31)
      - John B. Boles '65, 2004; 164183 (Box 22, Folder 32)
      - Harold R. Demoss, Jr. '52, 2004; 164184 (Box 22, Folder 33)
      - Jim Douglas, Jr. '50, '52, 2004; 164185 (Box 22, Folder 34)
      - Robert R. Maxfield '63, '64, 2004; 164186 (Box 22, Folder 35)
      - John J. Bertin '60, '62, '66, 2005; 164187 (Box 22, Folder 36)
      - Dorothy E. F. Carin '55, '74, 2005; 164188 (Box 22, Folder 37)
      - Lynn Laverty Elsenhans '78, 2005; 164189 (Box 22, Folder 38)
      - Vester T. Hughes, Jr. '49, 2005; 164190 (Box 22, Folder 39)
      - Robert M. Moody '61, 2005; 164191 (Box 22, Folder 40)
      - Helen Morris Havens '57, 2006; 164192 (Box 22, Folder 41)
      - Charles Redmon '64, '65, 2006; 164193 (Box 22, Folder 42)
      - Robert J. Saldich '55, '56, 2006; 164194 (Box 22, Folder 43)
      - Carroll Shaddock '62, 2006; 164195 (Box 22, Folder 44)
      - William N. Sick '57, '58, 2006; 164196 (Box 22, Folder 45)
      - Bill Arhos '57, 2007; 164197 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - James H. Newman '82, '84, 2007; 164198 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Arthur L. Storey, Jr. '59, 2007; 164199 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - George P. Taylor, Jr. '75, 2007; 164200 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - James S. Turley '77, '78, 2007; 164201 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Barbara B. Boyen '70, '74, '75, 2008; 164202 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Tom J. Fatjo, Jr. '63, 2008; 164203 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Nick C. Nichols '57, 2008; 164204 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Sam K. Reed '70, 2008; 164205 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - T. Jay Collins '70, 2009; 164206 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Rachelle Smith Doody '78, '92, 2009; 164207 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Robert Martin '71, 2009; 164208 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - Louis Brus '65, 2010; 164209 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - James Mischka '85, 2010; 164210 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Leslie H. Southwick '72, 2010; 164211 (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Peggy A. Whitson '86, 2010; 164212 (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - Keith T. Anderson '83, 2011; 164213 (Box 23, Folder 17)
      - Lida Kittrell Barrett '46, 2011; 164214 (Box 23, Folder 18)
      - Edward M. Emmett '71, 2011; 164215 (Box 23, Folder 19)
      - Malcolm R. O'Neill '70, '75, 2011; 164216 (Box 23, Folder 20)
      - Annise D. Parker '78, 2011; 164217 (Box 23, Folder 21)
      - Subha Barry '85, 2013; 215220 (Box 23, Folder 22)
      - Garrett Boone '66, 2013; 215223 (Box 23, Folder 23)
      - James Doty '62, 2013; 215224 (Box 23, Folder 24)
      - Sammy Ray '52 '54, 2013; 215233 (Box 23, Folder 25)
      - Pamela Scott '73, 2013; 215235 (Box 23, Folder 26)
      - George Hirasaki '67, 2014; 215227 (Box 23, Folder 27)
      - Libby Lehman '70, 2014; 215231 (Box 23, Folder 28)
      - Peter Rowe '71, 2014; 215234 (Box 23, Folder 29)
      - Rusty Williams '71, 2014; 215236 (Box 23, Folder 30)
      - Mary Lou Sauer Henry '61 [Restricted], 2014 (Box 23, Folder 31)
      - Sofia Adrogue [Restricted], 2014 (Box 23, Folder 32)
      - Gregory Curtis '66, 2015 (Box 23, Folder 33)
      - Robert Eury '72, '77, 2015 (Box 23, Folder 34)
      - Raymond Johnson '69, 2015 (Box 23, Folder 35)
      - Barbara Murray '69, 2015 (Box 23, Folder 36)
      - Lance Berkman '98, 2015; 215222 (Box 23, Folder 37)
      - William Russel [Restricted], 2015 (Box 23, Folder 38)
      - Richard Chapman [Restricted], 2015 (Box 23, Folder 39)
      - Cassie Barlow '96, 2016 (Box 23, Folder 40)
      - Anna Christy '98, 2016 (Box 23, Folder 41)
      - Ben Hollingsworth '64, 2016 (Box 23, Folder 42)
      - Virginia Moyer '74, 2016 (Box 23, Folder 43)
      - James M. Whitehurst [Restricted], 2016 (Box 23, Folder 44)
      - Gary Stern [Restricted], 2016 (Box 23, Folder 45)
      - Joshua Earnest '97, 2017 (Box 23, Folder 46)
      - N. Wayne Hale, Jr. '76, Nomination, 2017 (Box 23, Folder 47)
      - Diana McSherry, '67, '69, 2017 (Box 23, Folder 48)
      - Dr. Leland Winston, '69, 2017 (Box 23, Folder 49)
      - Cristle Collins Judd '83, '83, 2019 (Box 23, Folder 50)
      - Mark Durcan '83, '84, 2019 (Box 23, Folder 51)
      - Timothy Holy '91, 2019 (Box 23, Folder 52)
      - Dianna Milewicz '78, 2019 (Box 23, Folder 53)
      - Jim Blackburn, 2018 (Box 23, Folder 54)
      - ARA Laureates Pamphlets (Box 23, Folder 55)
      - Mrs. Charles Mays (Box 23, Folder 56)
      - Distinguished Owl Club Dinner, 2018 (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Gold Medal Award
    - Gold Medal Award Papers (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Gold Medal Award Recipients, 1950-2016; 164218
      - Allie Autry Kelley '25, 1950; 164219 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - George R. Brown '20, 1966; 164220 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Carey Croneis, 1967; 164221 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - George S. Cohen, 1969; 164222 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - J. Newton Rayzor, 1969; 164223 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - W. Maurice Ewing '26, 1972; 164224 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Samuel G. McMann, 1973; 164225 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Dominique de Menil, 1973; 164226 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - H. Malcolm Lovett '21, 1974; 164227 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Herbert C. Allen '29, 1975; 164228 (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - James U. Teague, '30, 1976; 164433 (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - Carl Illig '30, 1978; 164434 (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - E. Dell Butcher '34, 1979; 164435 (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Charles W. Duncan '47, 1979; 164436 (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - Arthur J. Hartsook ', 1980; 164437 (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - Stanley C. Moore '37, 1980; 164438 (Box 24, Folder 17)
      - Robert R. Herring, 1980; 164439 (Box 24, Folder 18)
      - Helen Saba Worden '38, 1981; 164440 (Box 24, Folder 19)
      - Josephine E. Abercrombie '46, 1982; 164441 (Box 24, Folder 20)
      - J. Street and Edythe Kingfulton, 1982; 164442 (Box 24, Folder 21)
      - Wendel D. Ley '32, 1983; 164443 (Box 24, Folder 22)
      - Norman Hackerman, 1984; 164444 (Box 24, Folder 23)
      - John L. Cox '45, 1985; 164445 (Box 24, Folder 24)
      - George H. Richter '26, 1985; 164446 (Box 24, Folder 25)
      - William E. Gordon, 1986; 164447 (Box 24, Folder 26)
      - C. M. "Hank" Hudspeth '40, 1986; 164461 (Box 24, Folder 27)
      - Ralph S. O'Connor, 1987; 164462 (Box 24, Folder 28)
      - Harry J. Chavanne '33, 1988; 164463 (Box 24, Folder 29)
      - Catherine Coburn Hannah '43, 1988; 164464 (Box 24, Folder 30)
      - Franz and Frances Brotzen, 1989; 164465 (Box 24, Folder 31)
      - David E. Farnsworth '42, 1989; 164466 (Box 24, Folder 32)
      - Captain James A. Baker, 1990; 164467 (Box 24, Folder 33)
      - Burton J. McMurtry '56, 1990; 164468 (Box 24, Folder 34)
      - S.I. Morris '35, 1991; 164469 (Box 24, Folder 35)
      - J. Thomas Eubank '51, 1992; 164470 (Box 24, Folder 36)
      - Katherine T. Brown '38, 1994; 164471 (Box 24, Folder 37)
      - Kenneth S. Pitzer, 1994; 164472 (Box 24, Folder 38)
      - George R. Miner '50, 1995; 164473 (Box 24, Folder 39)
      - Al and Bridget Jansen '52 and '53, 1996; 164474 (Box 24, Folder 40)
      - J. Evans Atwell '53, 1997; 164475 (Box 24, Folder 41)
      - Michael P. Hammond, 1998; 164476 (Box 24, Folder 42)
      - Paul E. Pfeiffer '38, '48, '52, 1998; 164477 (Box 24, Folder 43)
      - D. Kent Anderson '62, 1999; 164478 (Box 24, Folder 44)
      - Alan J. Chapman '45, 1999; 164479 (Box 24, Folder 45)
      - Ronald and Mona Stebbings, 2000; 164480 (Box 24, Folder 46)
      - William P. Hobby '53 and Diana Hobby '81, 2001; 164481 (Box 24, Folder 47)
      - Hershel and Hilda Rich '45, '47/ '48, 2002; 164482 (Box 24, Folder 48)
      - Joyce Pounds Hardy-McDonald '45, 2003; 164483 (Box 24, Folder 49)
      - G. King Walters '53, 2003; 164484 (Box 24, Folder 50)
      - Elizabeth Gillis, 2004; 164485 (Box 24, Folder 51)
      - Malcolm Gillis, 2004; 164486 (Box 24, Folder 52)
      - E. William Barnett '55, 2005; 164487 (Box 24, Folder 53)
      - Gilbert R. Whitaker, Jr. '53, 2005; 164488 (Box 24, Folder 54)
      - J.D. Bucky Allshouse '71, 2006; 164489 (Box 24, Folder 55)
      - Ronald L. Sass, 2006; 164490 (Box 24, Folder 56)
      - C Sidney Burns and Mary Lee Burrus '57, '58, 2007; 164491 (Box 24, Folder 57)
      - James A. Baker III, 2008; 164492 (Box 24, Folder 58)
      - Edward P. Djerejian, 2009; 164493 (Box 24, Folder 59)
      - Neal Lane, 2009; 164494 (Box 24, Folder 60)
      - Allen J. Matusow, 2010; 164495 (Box 24, Folder 61)
      - Raymond D. Brochstein '55, '56, 2011; 164496 (Box 24, Folder 62)
      - Robert F. Curl '54, 2011; 164497 (Box 24, Folder 63)
      - James Crownover '65 '66, 2013; 215207 (Box 24, Folder 64)
      - Wayne Graham, 2013; 215213 (Box 24, Folder 65)
      - Melbern '61 & Susie Glasscock '62, 2014; 215209 (Box 24, Folder 66)
      - Robert L. Clarke '63, 2015 (Box 24, Folder 67)
      - Lynn Elsenhans '78 [Restricted], 2015 (Box 24, Folder 68)
      - Karen George '77 '78, 2016 (Box 24, Folder 69)
      - Gus Schill '55, 2016 (Box 24, Folder 70)
      - Dennis Huston [Restricted], 2016 (Box 24, Folder 71)
      - Bruce W. Dunlevie '79, 2019 (Box 24, Folder 72)
      - Mary McIntire '75, 2019 (Box 24, Folder 73)
      - James Burch '68, 2019 (Box 24, Folder 74)
      - H. Russell Pitman (Box 24, Folder 75)
  - Meritorious Service Award
    - Meritorious Award Papers (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Photos and Descriptions of Meritorious Service Award Recipients for Display, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Meritorious Service Award Recipients, 1986-2016; 164520
      - Margaret S. Alsbrook, 1986; 164521 (Box 25, Folder 3)